We have the 112th pick on the line right
now. Drew Shelton, offensive tackle from
Penn State. Drew, congratulations on the
moment. Welcome to being a part of the
Dallas Cowboys organization. Just tell
us what's going through your head at the
moment.
>> I'm just so thankful and so excited to
get, you know, be a part of the Cowboys.
You know, such a a storied program and
um just ready to get a part be a part of
it. This is a an organization that has
always taken the offensive line very
very seriously going back to the five
Super Bowls that they've won. What does
it mean to you to to be a part of that?
And what are Cowboys fans going to get
in your offensive line play?
>> You know, you're going to get a guy
that's going to come to work every
single day trying to get better. Um, do
everything I can, you know, help our
quarterbacks, help our running backs,
and do whatever this team needs me to do
to succeed.
when you were having conversations with
the the Cowboys staff, Clayton Adams or
Connor Riley, Brian Shottimer, uh, one,
who were some of the guys that you were
talking to, uh, but what were those
conversations about and how they'll use
you moving forward?
>> Yeah, I have to talk to Coach Riley. Um,
you know, he recruited me out of high
school actually at Kansas State and
then, you know, got the chance to sit
down with him at Penn State. Um, and
then just, you know, I'm I'm excited to
play for him. Um he's a great coach and
he's going to get the best out of me
every single day.
>> You uh played at IMG Academy. Did Did
you Were you there? Were you teammates
with Tyler Booker? Are you guys
reuniting?
>> Yeah, I was there in the spring semester
with Book.
>> That's awesome. What was that
relationship like?
>> You know, he he's the main reason I went
down there. Uh
>> nice book's a great dude. He's a
competitor. You know, he's he's a great
ball player, too. So, I'm excited to get
back down there with him.
We've got the offensive tackle out of
Penn State on the line. Uh Drew Shelton,
the 112th overall pick here in this
year's NFL draft. Uh lots of really good
Penn State offensive linemen have come
out recently. Who are some of the guys
that helped mentor you once you arrived
on on campus up there in PA?
>> Yeah, I think of guys like Drew Scrugs
who's now with the Lions and Olu Fashion
um with the Jets. They both kind of took
me under their wing and you know really
good football players in college and
turning into that in the pros as well.
>> The draft process in in its entirety
does kind of seem like a bit of a grind.
Drew for you. How's it been? And really
how much contact did you have with
Dallas leading up to this pick today?
>> Yeah, it's it's been u it's been a long
process. It's been fun. Um I put my
hamstring into the combine. It's just
not ideal. So limited me a little bit,
but um I had a private workout with the
Cowboys and you know really went from
there. That was about it.
>> And one thing that we've seen on your
tape is you do have some some swing
opportunity, left tackle, right tackle.
How comfortable are you in either one of
those situations and what do you expect
going forward based off of the
conversations you've had?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm pretty comfortable doing
both. Um, you know, I I played mainly
left tackle at Penn State, but I've been
training to do both ever since the uh
last game of my last season. So, I'm I'm
ready. I'm excited for the opportunity
and just looking forward to it.
>> Now, you are coming into this, you are
now going to be teammates with the top
pick, Caleb DS. You obviously went up
against Ohio State several times. Was
there uh do you remember how difficult
he was to the game plans that you guys
were trying to do on offense? Was Caleb
DS just wrecking shop for you guys?
Yeah, he can do a lot. Um, really good
player, really instinctual, really fast.
Uh, I remember some screen plays he
would just blow him up just because, you
know, he read it before anyone else and
he was able to use his speed and get
there. So, really good player, really
excited to get to play with him.
>> Same thing you could say for for Jan
Baram. How did you ever get the chance
to go up against Barum who was picked in
the third round?
>> Yeah, we played against him when he was
at Maryland a couple years ago. Um,
another really good player. Really good
player.
>> There you go. Well, we appreciate you
taking some time. Congratulations again
being the 112th pick. It's I know it's a
great day for you and your family. Drew,
uh, take care. We'll see you soon down
here in Fris.
>> Yes, sir. Thank you.
>> There he goes. Drew Shelton, offensive
tackle from Penn State, where the
Cowboys took him in the fourth round at
pick number 112. We got to step aside
for a minute. The Cowboys are getting
closer and closer to their final
selection of the fourth round to pick
number 137.